3playmedia.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy – 3Play Media

**Last updated: July 16, 2019**

## Overview

This privacy policy describes our data collection, usage, and dissemination practices and applies to our websites, account system, plugins, and tools.

The section Privacy for 3Play Media Site explains our policies with respect to the information we collect and manage when you visit www.3playmedia.com and other websites (collectively referred to as the “Site”).

The section Privacy for the 3Play Media System explains our policies with respect to the information we collect and manage when you create an account and interact with 3Play Media’s tools, plugins, and other products and services (collectively referred to as the “System”).

The section How to Manage Cookies explains how to enable and disable cookies on the Site.

By using the Site or the System, you consent to the practices described in this privacy policy.

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy and safety of children. The Site and System are not intended for children under the age of 16 (who reside in the EU, the European Economic Area or Switzerland) and children under the age of 13 (who reside in the United States).

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time.

## Privacy for 3Play Media Site

### Information We May Collect

We may collect the following information about you:

  * Data submitted by you, such as your e-mail address, name, and telephone number. We may combine this information with publicly available information.
  * Data submitted by you through a job application form.
  * Data submitted by you through a survey.
  * IP address and device ID.
  * Information about your computer hardware and software, such as computer type and screen resolution.
  * Certain types of demographic information.
  * Web page analytics and usage information, such as web page activity, links clicked, and videos watched.
  * Geolocation data.

Some of this information, including the IP address, is stored in our log files along with the date and time.

#### Cookies

We may use cookies and related technologies to collect information about you, improve the site, communicate with you, and provide targeted information to you. Cookies help us to personalize your online experience. If you choose to decline cookies, you will not fully experience the features of the Site. Most Internet browsers have options for controlling, disabling, and deleting cookies on your computer. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by third parties.

#### Email Tracking

We may use tracking pixels and other technologies to track when emails have been opened and which links in an email have been clicked. This helps us to measure the performance of our email campaigns and provide you with more targeted information.

#### Advertising

We may work with third parties to manage our advertising on third-party websites, which may include serving or tracking advertisements relating to the Site. Our third-party service providers may use cookies and other technologies to gather information about your activities on the Site and third-party sites in order to serve you targeted advertising. The privacy policies of those third parties will govern your interactions with those third-party websites or ad networks. Many ad networks have joined the Digital Advertising Alliance’s self-regulatory program to provide a single [opt-out](http://www.aboutads.info/). The European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA) provides a similar [opt-out](http://youronlinechoices.eu/).

#### Forums

The Site may include message boards, forums, chat functionality, profile pages, and blogs to which you are able to post information and materials (collectively referred to as the “Forums”). Please note that any information you disclose through the Forums may be available to visitors to the Site and to the general public. Please exercise discretion and caution while using the Forums. We are not responsible for the use of any information you disclose through your use of the Forums.

#### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to collect and processes information about you and how you interact with the Site. You can [opt out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) from Google’s collection of information.

#### Do Not Track

The Site does not recognize your browser’s “do not track” setting to indicate that you do not wish to be tracked.

#### Security

We use organizational, technical, and administrative measures to protect personal information under our control. When you submit information through a form on the Site, we encrypt the transmission of that information. However, no data transmission over the Internet or any other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Site, we do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit.

### How We May Use Your Information

We may use your information in the following ways:

  * To fulfill your requests.
  * To communicate with you about the information you requested.
  * To contact you and send you emails that may be of interest to you.
  * To contact you via surveys about your opinion of current services or of potential new services.
  * To infer whether you are a good candidate for our products and services.
  * To remember information you entered on the Site.
  * To improve our websites, services, and products.
  * To customize the content you see.
  * To conduct research and provide anonymous statistical reporting.

### How Your Information May Be Shared

We may share your information with our trusted partners who work on our behalf or with whom we collaborate. These partners may use your information to communicate with you directly or help us communicate with you.

We may work with ad networks that display targeted advertisements based on your information. These ad networks may make inferences based on this information in order to provide targeted ads. They may collect and aggregate information about you or make inferences based on your information to serve targeted ads to you.

### How to Opt Out from Emails

If you do not want to receive emails from us, you can [opt out or change your preferences](https://go.3playmedia.com/email-subscription-preferences) any time.

### Data Retention

We retain your information for the period of time appropriate for us to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes or enforce our agreements, whichever is longer.

### Right to Request Information

You may request, and we will provide you with, information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may request access to, or correction or deletion of your personal information, by contacting us at [privacy@3playmedia.com](mailto:privacy@3playmedia.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

### General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Rights

The following section applies to residents of the European Union, European Economic Area, or Switzerland who visit the Site.

3Play Media processes data for the purposes as set forth in this privacy policy. Our lawful bases for the processing of personal data are: (i) consent and/or (ii) any other applicable lawful bases, such as our legitimate interest in engaging in commerce, offering products and services of value to the users of the Site, preventing fraud, ensuring information and network security, marketing and complying with industry practices.

Residents of applicable countries have the following rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):

  * To withdraw consent to processing, where consent is the basis of processing. You may withdraw your consent to processing by leaving the Site, suspending your account if you have registered on the Site, or requesting that we delete your personal information.
  * To access the personal information we have collected about you.
  * To demand rectification of inaccurate personal information about you.
  * To object to unlawful data processing.
  * To erasure of past information about you.
  * To demand that we restrict processing of your personal information, if you believe we have exceeded the legitimate basis for processing, processing is no longer necessary, or your personal information is inaccurate.
  * To receive the personal information we have collected about you in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format.
  * To lodge a complaint to a data protection supervisory authority in your country.

To exercise any of the above-listed rights, please contact us at [privacy@3playmedia.com](mailto:privacy@3playmedia.com). We will process any requests in accordance with applicable law and within a reasonable period of time. We may need to verify your identity before processing your request.

To learn more about your rights under the GDPR you can visit the European Commission’s page on Protection of Personal Data, at: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/index_en.htm>

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@3playmedia.com](mailto:privacy@3playmedia.com), or call +1 617-764-5189.

## Privacy for 3Play Media System

### Information We May Collect

We may collect the following information about you:

  * Contact and billing information.
  * Login credentials.
  * IP address and device ID.
  * Information about your computer hardware and software, such as computer type and screen resolution.
  * Web page analytics and usage information
  * Geolocation data.
  * Data submitted by you through a survey.

Some of this information, including the IP address, is stored in our log files along with the date and time.

#### Payment Processing

We use a third party payment service to process credit card payments. When you provide credit card information on the Site, that information is sent directly to the payment service. We do not have access to your full credit card number and do not store that information. Information transmitted to the payment service is encrypted using SSL software and the payment service is required to comply with all applicable privacy and security laws and the rules and regulations issued by the credit card companies. We are not responsible for the payment service’s failure to comply with such laws, rules and regulations.

#### Cookies

We may use certain persistent first-party cookies to provide the best user experience and remember your preferences with the 3Play Media system. Most Internet browsers have options for controlling, disabling, and deleting cookies on your computer.

#### Email Tracking

We may use tracking pixels and other technologies to track when emails have been opened and which links in an email have been clicked. This helps us to measure the performance of our email campaigns and provide you with more targeted information.

#### Forums

The System may include message boards, support forums, chat functionality, profile pages, and blogs to which you are able to post information and materials (collectively referred to as the “Forums”). Please note that any information you disclose through the Forums may be available to visitors to the Site and to the general public. Please exercise discretion and caution while using the Forums. We are not responsible for the use of any information you disclose through your use of the Forums.

#### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to collect and processes information about you and how you interact with the System. You can [opt out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) from Google’s collection of information.

#### Do Not Track

The Site does not recognize your browser’s “do not track” setting to indicate that you do not wish to be tracked.

#### Security

All data is encrypted at rest, in backups, and in transit using SSL protocols. It is also possible for personal information about EU residents to be contained in media which is uploaded to the Site, and with the resulting transcripts we produce. We assume that any such information transmitted to our system has been approved by our customers as transmittable and store-able, subject to the above constraints.

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

Learn more about our [security](https://www.3playmedia.com/solutions/how-it-works/security/) policies.

How We May Use Your Information  
We may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To deliver services and fulfill your requests.
  * To provide customer support.
  * To communicate with you and send you information and updates about our services, programs, and promotions.
  * For internal business purposes, including data analysis, developing new products, enhancing our services, conducting research, and identifying usage trends.
  * To protect the security and integrity of our products and services.
  * To meet our contractual requirements, to comply with applicable legal or regulatory requirements and our policies and to protect against criminal activity, claims and other liabilities.
  * In other ways with appropriate consent.

### How Your Information May Be Shared

We may share your information in the following ways:

  * With third-party service providers we use to support our business. These parties include third parties providing us with services such as website hosting, data analysis, infrastructure provision, IT services, customer service, analytics and email delivery services. These third parties are authorized to use information only to the extent necessary to provide these services to us.
  * With our current affiliates and any future corporate subsidiaries or affiliates.
  * With a buyer, investor, new affiliate or other third party in the event that 3Play Media, or any portion, group or business unit thereof, undergoes a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition, or during steps in contemplation of such activities.
  * With third parties for marketing, advertising, promotions, contests or other similar purposes. If required by applicable law, we will share such data for advertising and marketing purposes only in an aggregate, anonymous and de-identified manner.
  * To comply with any law or directive, judicial or administrative order, legal process or investigation, warrant, subpoena, law enforcement or national security investigation, or as otherwise required or authorized by law; to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside the country of residence; to enforce our policies, terms and conditions; to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates, customers, partners, agents or others; to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property and/or that of our affiliates, customers, partners, agents and any other person or organization; and/or to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

### How to Opt Out from Emails

If you do not want to receive marketing emails from us, you can [opt out or change your preferences](https://go.3playmedia.com/email-subscription-preferences) any time. You may not opt out of communications required for operational and billing purposes.

### Data Retention

We may retain information for as long as the account of the user for whom we collected the information is active, or as long as is reasonably necessary to provide our services, or as needed for other lawful purposes. We may retain cached or archived copies of information. We may retain anonymized or pseudonymized aggregated data indefinitely. We also will retain information as long as reasonably necessary for accounting/billing/tax purposes or to comply with our contractual and/or legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

### Right to Request Information

You may request, and we will provide you with, information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may request access to, or correction or deletion of your personal information, by contacting us at [privacy@3playmedia.com](mailto:privacy@3playmedia.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

### General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Rights

The following section applies to residents of the European Union, European Economic Area, or Switzerland who visit the Site.

3Play Media processes data for the purposes as set forth in this privacy policy. Our lawful bases for the processing of personal data are: (i) consent and/or (ii) any other applicable lawful bases, such as our legitimate interest in engaging in commerce, offering products and services of value to the users of the System, preventing fraud, ensuring information and network security, marketing and complying with industry practices.

Residents of applicable countries have the following rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):

  * To request a copy of the personal information we have collected about you by contacting us as directed below.
  * To request that we rectify or delete any personal information about you that is incomplete, incorrect, unnecessary or outdated.
  * To object to personal information being processed for marketing purposes without your consent.
  * To receive the personal information we have collected about you in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format.
  * To lodge a complaint to a data protection supervisory authority in your country.
  * To withdraw consent if the personal information we collected is processed solely based on your consent and not for any other legitimate interest.

To exercise any of the above-listed rights, please contact us at [privacy@3playmedia.com](mailto:privacy@3playmedia.com). We will process any requests in accordance with applicable law and within a reasonable period of time. We may need to verify your identity before processing your request.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@3playmedia.com](mailto:privacy@3playmedia.com), or call +1 617-764-5189.

## How to Manage Cookies

Cookies help you to get the most out of our website. If you disable our cookies you may find that certain sections of our website do not work like they are supposed to.

#### How to Disable Advertising Cookies

If you are concerned about advertising cookies, users in the European Union can visit [youronlinechoices.eu](http://youronlinechoices.eu/) and users in the US can visit [aboutads.info/choices](http://aboutads.info/choices) to opt out of these third party cookies.

#### How to Enable and Disable Cookies Using Your Browser

Most browsers allow you to manage cookie settings. These settings can usually be found in the Settings, Options or Preferences menu of your browser. The links below are provided to help you find the settings for some common browsers.

Manage cookie settings in [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en) and [Chrome Android](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&co=GENIE.Platform%3DAndroid&oco=1) and [Chrome iOS](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&co=GENIE.Platform%3DiOS&oco=1)  
Manage cookie settings in [Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?locale=en_US) and [Safari iOS](https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT201265)  
Manage cookie settings in [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)  
Manage cookie settings in [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies)  
Manage cookie settings in [Opera](http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/)  
For all other browsers, please look for a “help” function in your browser or contact the browser provider.

### Learn More

To learn more about your rights under the GDPR you can visit the European Commission’s page on Protection of Personal Data, at: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/index_en.htm>

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@3playmedia.com](mailto:privacy@3playmedia.com), or call +1 617-764-5189.
